webassessor.com 2002-12-02

# DKI Privacy Statement

|  |   
---|---  
  |   | 

#### Drake Kryterion, Inc.  
Online Privacy Policy

By using the Drake Kryterion, Inc, "DKI" Web site, you agree to the terms of the DKI Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use this site.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
At times, particularly when you order products, download software, or enter contests from the DKI Web site, DKI may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to participate in these programs. If you elect to participate in these programs, however, DKI may require that you provide your contact information, which may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information.

When you submit personal information to DKI, you understand and agree that DKI and its affiliates and vendors may transfer, store, and process your customer profile in any of the countries in which DKI or its affiliates or vendors maintain offices, including without limitation, the United States.

DKI collects this information in order to record and support your participation in the programs you select. If you order a product, for example, the information is used to register your license and rights, if any, to technical support, upgrade discounts, or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. If you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and to contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. DKI also uses information that you provide as part of our effort to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other DKI products and services.

DKI recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of this information. If you do not want the information you provide to DKI to be used to inform you of other products and special offers from DKI, and you indicate this preference when you provide the information to DKI, DKI will honor your preference. In addition, DKI may selectively provide certain information to other companies or organizations that have products or services we think may interest you. If you do not want the information you provide to DKI to be shared with other companies, and you indicate this preference when you provide the information to DKI, DKI will honor your preference.

**Use of Cookies**  
When you visit DKI Web site, you can surf the site anonymously and access important information about DKI products without revealing your identity. In order to improve the DKI site, we may use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, recording your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You should be aware that for some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.

While DKI uses cookies to track your visit to Drake Kryterion, and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided DKI with personal information.

**Updating Your Personal Information**  
You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by writing to DKI at

_Drake Kryterion, Inc.  
Attn: Customer Service  
7776 South Pointe Parkway West  
Suite 250  
Phoenix, AZ 85044 USA_

Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us.

Please note that DKI is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-DKI Web sites to which DKI or any other DKI Web site may link.

|
